Nataliya Rodionova

Web Designer • Illiustrator • Web Developer

EXPERIENCE

2019 • WEB DESIGNER

FREELANCE

Developing innovative concepts for the website design and implement them in the form of attractive designs.

Creating responsive websites, designing elements such as layout, fonts, colors, images and animations in such a way that they reflect customer needs and the corporate identity of our customers.

2017 - 2018 • **FASHION DESIGNER**

PARIS MILAN SHOWROOM VARONA BY NATALIYA RODIONOVA SS18 FW18

Creating visual concepts, sketches, and samples for review. Autonomous creation of patterns and prototypes. Production of garments in shuttle fabric, jersey and knitwear. Presentation of the collection in the Showroom.

2017 - 2018 • **FASHION DESIGNER**

UKRAINIAN FASHION WEEK SPRING/SUMMER 2019 VARONA BY NATALIYA RODIONOVA

Conceptualizing clothing for characters and cast. Conducting research on fabrics, trims and various industry standard techniques.

Creating visual concepts, sketches, and samples for review. Autonomous creation of patterns and prototypes. Execution of tailoring a prototype of fashion collection. Organizing a fashion week show:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PPzNoMCWNik

2016 - 2017 • **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

CATTEL SPA

Responsible for the design of artwork for agency projects, signs, flyers, brochures, posters, billboards, logos, exhibits/displays, and illustrations. Design, layout, revise, edit, and produce

various publications (print and digital versions).

2016 - 2017 • RETAIL SALES ASSISTANT

DOLCE&GABBANA MICHAEL KORS CORSOCOMO10 MARNI PINKO ARMANI

CRM activities.

Promoting and selling products to international customers. Developing outstanding customer service and building long-term relationship with customers.



ABOUT ME

Hi. My name is Nataliya Rodionova. I have studied at Marangoni Design Institute in Milan. After graduating I worked as a stylist and seller in a Multicultural capital Fashion and then after the pandemic I worked for 5 years as a freelancer in Web and Graphic Design. In 2022, I moved to Berlin. I am now in my final phase of the DCI course in Web Development and I am searching for a Job as a Web Developer. I am sure that my sales experience, creativity, and design skills can benefit a lot to the company and help to make the website or application very unique.

CONTACT

ADRESS

Schöneberge Ufer 53, 10785 Berlin

PHONE

+491639436453

EMAIL

Nataliyarodionova26@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO

behance.net/nataliyrodiono https://github.com/006080

EDUCATION

2016 - 2017 • WEB DEVELOPMENT

DCI, BERLIN

Basic Digital Literacy / UI Basics / Programming Basics / Single Page Application / Backend

2014- 2015 • ILLUSTRATION

NABA, MILAN

Developing the technical skills and the ability to organize the visual elements necessary to communicate concepts and experiences across various software.

Producing attractive illustrations for print and social media.

2014- 2015 • **FASHION DESIGN**

MARANGONI ISTITUTE, MILAN

Learning the tools and the design approach specific to a fashion designer.

Improving the skills to analyse and develop concepts and ideas, which later will be used in complex projects, managing all the steps of the design and the making phase.

2005 - 2010 • FASHION MODELLING

ZNTU, ZAPORIZHZHYE

Management Marketing

2016 - 2017 • FASHION MODELLING

VPTU 38, ZAPORIZHZHYE

Tailoring course Pattern - making MENSWEAR / WOMENSWEAR

1990 - 1998 • MUSIC SCHOOL

PIANO

REVIEWS

https://freelancehunt.com/my/reviews

https://free lance hunt.com/contest/raz rabotka-logotipa-firmen nogo-stilya-dlya/5414.html

https://freelancehunt.com/contest/kvartalnyiy-kalendar-dlya-gruzovogo-tehtsentra/5417.html

SKILLS

Adobe Ps ••••• Adobe Ai ••••• Adobe Id ••••• Adobe Xd Adobe Ae ••••• Figma ••••• HTML ••••• **CSS** ••••• Javascript React Node.js ••••• Mongo DB •••••

LANGUEGE

Russian

Ukrainian

English

Italian

HOBBIES

German







